<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Holistic Habits Coaching</title>
    <link>https://holistichabits.fit/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Holistic Habits Coaching</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 19:17:23 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://holistichabits.fit/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Your Blueprint to Losing Weight, Feeling Good, and Looking Great in Your Skin</title>
      <link>https://holistichabits.fit/blog/your_fat_loss_blueprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 06:11:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://holistichabits.fit/blog/your_fat_loss_blueprint/</guid>
      <description>What would I do if I woke up one day overweight, out of shape, and ready to make a change? Although it would seem daunting at first, with the right plan, I am confident I could knock it out in no time! And today I&amp;rsquo;m going to share my personal roadmap to getting back into shape as quickly as possible while feeling good along the way. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive right in!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Blueberry and Matcha Overnight Oats</title>
      <link>https://holistichabits.fit/blog/blueberry_matcha_overnight_oats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 17:06:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://holistichabits.fit/blog/blueberry_matcha_overnight_oats/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 60g frozen blueberries 60g frozen raspberries 1 medium kiwifruit 150g greek yogurt (whole milk) 25g vanilla whey protein (80%) 225ml almond milk 45g oats 3 tsp honey 1 1/2 tsp chia seeds 1 tsp matcha powder Preparation Prepare the night before and you&amp;rsquo;ll wake up like it’s your birthday every day!
In a small bowl, whisk the matcha and warm water (2 tbsp) together until a smooth consistency is formed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Nutrition Practices to Avoid (If You Actually Wanted to Make Progress)</title>
      <link>https://holistichabits.fit/blog/8_nutrition_practices_to_avoid_if_you_actually_wanted_to_make_progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 19:01:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://holistichabits.fit/blog/8_nutrition_practices_to_avoid_if_you_actually_wanted_to_make_progress/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re serious about actually making progress and achieving sustainable results for your health and overall well-being, then it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to be aware of the pitfalls that lie ahead. In the realm of modern diet culture, there are certain approaches that may promise quick results on the scale, but beware! These seemingly enticing strategies can actually wreck your metabolism and lead to an increase in body fat percentage over the long haul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cure for Modern Life</title>
      <link>https://holistichabits.fit/blog/the_cure_for_modern_life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 19:25:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://holistichabits.fit/blog/the_cure_for_modern_life/</guid>
      <description>Picture this: You wake up in the morning and groggily reach for your phone, instantly bombarded by a deluge of notifications. As you navigate through your day, you find yourself sitting at your desk, hunched over a screen for hours on end. Meetings, presentations, and deadlines keep you tethered to your seat, as the world outside passes by unnoticed. The only physical activity you get is the brief walk from your car to the office, and even that feels like a fleeting moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Power of a Nutritional Plan</title>
      <link>https://holistichabits.fit/blog/unlocking_the_power_of_a_nutritional_plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 20:55:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://holistichabits.fit/blog/unlocking_the_power_of_a_nutritional_plan/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of starting your week with lofty health goals, only to find yourself face-first in a bag of chips by Wednesday? It&amp;rsquo;s time to break free from this vicious cycle and discover the secret to maintaining a healthy lifestyle, even when life gets crazy. In this eye-opening article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the importance of having a well-crafted nutritional plan and how it can save you from becoming a hangry monster during those hectic weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
